[{"answer": "Fortunate girl. At least she can escape Fanny, which is more than any of us is able", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " I have! I have said 'yes' and 'no'", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Of course. The Volga, which, as you know, starts in..", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "We cannot even earn ours", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Excellent fellow! We served in the that place together", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Reclusive individual. But you are fatigued. I can see that you are fatigued", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "That is not the point. You do not speak of such things before stranger", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend is not everyone", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Decent sho", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Like", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "How do you do", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Welcome to our party, Miss my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "This reproach from you! You, who confide in no one", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Nor I. We have neither of us anything to tell. I because I conceal nothing and you because you communicate nothing", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Not so unworthy! Did he tell you that he loved you", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He has broken faith with all of us, he made us all believe he loved you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend, there is no excuse for hi", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "There is no one to take us", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "How does your sister", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Then permit me to accompany you and take you straight on from that place to my friend myself", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why have you taken so long to come and see us", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Engaged elsewhere! But what was that when there were such friends to be met", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "How can that possibly be", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "But I have no dowry", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "We shall be home soon enough. Mamma will comfort you, dearest", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I think it is going to rain", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Shall we continue tomorrow", "docId": "Sense-and-Sensibility.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Away? Where", "qsentId": 30}]